[Music]
any unauthorized license that they issue
will not have my name my title or my
authority on
it so you're telling me Kim Davis is
collecting a government paycheck in
order to sit around and let everyone
else do all the
work I thought we called people like
that welfare
Queens wait got it got it got it got it
stop stop it stop it now
okay how are you shooting machine guns
in front of a government building
without getting
arrested we
we're can you not see us see
you it's great you can't spar with him
though he has no filter he'll say
whatever you know what I'm saying no
that is true like you trying to be you
know keep things above board talking
about what about your ridiculous
immigration policies and he's like shut
up
fatty we're not talk we're not having
the same
conversation hey America Larry Wilmore
here if you like the nightly show on
Comedy Central like us on Facebook too
just don't poke me I do not like being
poked you can Candy Crush me